const javaLanguage =[
    {
        question: "Number of primitive data types in Java are?stion ",
        ans: 4, 
        option: [
             " 6",
             " 7",
             " 8",
             " 8",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "To which of the following does the class string belong to. ",
        ans: 1, 
        option: [
          "java.lang",
          " java.awt",
          " java.applet",
          " java.string",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "Total constructor string class have? ",
        ans: 3, 
        option: [
          "3",
          "7",
          "13",
          "20",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "  Where does the system stores parameters and local variables whenever a method is invoked? ",
        ans: 2, 
        option: [
          "Heap",
          "Stack",
          "Array ",
          " Tree",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "What is the implicit return type of constructor?  ",
        ans:2, 
        option: [
          "No return type",
          " Aclass object in which it is defined",
          " Void",
          " None",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "Exception created by try block is caught in which block ",
        ans: 1, 
        option: [
          "catch",
          " throw",
          "final",
          " none",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "  Which of the following exception is thrown when divided by zero statement is executed?",
        ans: 3, 
        option: [
          "NullPointrException",
          " NumberFormatException",
          " ArithmaticExceotion",
          " None",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "  Where is System class defined? ",
        ans: 1, 
        option: [
          "java.lang.package",
          " java.util.package",
          " java.io.package",
          "None",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "  Identify the interface which is used to declare core methods in java ",
        ans: 4, 
        option: [
          " Comparator",
          " EventListener",
          " Set",
          " Collection",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        question: "  Which of the following is used to find and fix bugs in the program? ",
        ans: 4, 
        option: [
          "JDK",
          " JRE",
          " JVM",
          " JDB",
         
        ],
      },
      
    ];
   
    console.log(javaLanguage.question)
